A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Press Office records, 2001-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. News summaries, 2003-2006 (Accessions 41072, 41239, 41692, 42461).
  - 2003 (Accession 41072)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 9 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 10 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 11 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 12 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 13 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 14 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 15 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 16 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 17 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 18 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 19 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 20 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 21 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 22 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 23 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 24 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 25 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 26 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 27 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 28 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 29 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 30 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 31 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 4 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 4 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 5 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 5 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 6 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 7 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 8 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 9 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 10 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 11 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 12 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 13 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 14 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 15 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 16 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 17 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 18 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 19 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 22 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 23 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 24 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 25 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 26 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 27 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 28 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 29 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Nov. 30 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 2 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 3 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 4 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 5 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 6 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 7 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 8 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 9 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 10 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 11 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 12 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 13 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 14 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 15 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 16 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 17 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 18 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 19 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 20 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 21 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 22 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 23 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 24 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 25 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 26 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 27 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 28 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 29 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 30 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Dec. 31 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - 2004 Jan. 1 - May 16 (Accession 41239)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 3 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 4 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 5 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 6 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 7 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 8 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 9 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 10 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 11 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 12 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 13 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 14 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 15 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 15 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 16 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 16 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 17 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 18 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 19 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 20 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 20 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 21 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 22 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 22 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 23 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 24 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 25 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 26 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 27 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 28 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 29 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 29 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 30 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 30 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Jan. 31 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 2 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 3 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 3 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 4 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 4 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 5 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 5 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 6 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 6 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 7 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 8 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 9 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 9 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 10 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 10 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 11 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 11 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 12 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 13 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 13 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 14 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 15 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 15 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 16 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 17 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 17 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 18 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 18 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 19 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 20 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 20 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 21 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 22 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 23 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 24 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 25 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 25 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 26 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 26 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 27 (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 27 (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 28 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Feb. 29 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 2 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 3 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 3 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 4 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 4 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 5 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 5 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 6 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 7 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 8 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 9 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 10 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 10 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 11 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 11 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 12 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 12 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 13 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 14 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 15 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 15 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 16 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 16 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 17 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 17 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 18 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 19 (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 19 (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 20 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 21 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 22 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 23 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 24 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 25 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 25 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 26 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 26 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 27 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 28 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 29 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 30 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 30 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 31 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Mar. 31 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 1 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 1 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 2 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 2 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 3 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 4 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 5 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 6 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 6 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 7 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 8 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 9 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 10 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 11 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 12 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 13 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 13 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 14 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 14 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 15 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 16 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 16 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 17 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 18 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 19 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 20 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 20 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 22 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 23 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 24 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 25 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 26 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 27 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 27 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 28 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 29 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 29 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Apr. 30 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 5 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 6 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 7 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 8 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 9 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 10 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 11 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 12 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 13 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 14 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 15 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 16 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 16 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 2004 May 17 - 2005 Jan. (Accession 41692)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 17 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 18 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 19 (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 19 (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 20 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 21 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 22 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 23 (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 23 (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 24 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 25 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 26 (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 26 (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 27 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 28 (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 28 (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 29 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 30 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 1 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 2 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 3 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 4 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 5 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 6 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 7 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 8 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 9 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 10 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 11 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 12 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 13 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 14 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 15 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 16 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 17 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 18 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 19 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 20 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 21 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 22 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 23 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 24 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 25 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 26 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 27 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 28 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 29 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 June 30 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 1 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 2 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 3 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 4 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 5 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 6 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 7 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 8 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 9 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 10 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 11 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 12 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 13 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 14 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 15 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 16 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 17 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 18 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 19 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 20 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 21 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 22 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 23 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 24 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 25 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 26 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 27 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 28 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 29 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 30 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 July 31 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 1 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 2 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 3 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 4 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 5 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 6 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 7 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 8 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 9 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 10 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 11 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 12 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 13 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 14 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 15 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 16 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 17 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 18 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 19 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 20 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 21 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 22 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 23 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 24 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 25 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 26 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 27 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 28 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 29 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 30 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Aug. 31 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 1 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 3 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 4 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 5 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 6 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 7 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 8 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 9 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 10 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 11 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 12 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 13 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 14 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 15 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 16 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 17 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 18 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 19 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 20 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 21 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 22 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 23 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 25 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 26 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 27 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 28 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 29 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2004 Sept. 30 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 1 (1 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 1 (2 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 2 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 3 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 4 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 5 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 6 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 7 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 8 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2004 Oct. 9 (Box 48, Folder 14)